GRACE GRUMO

Makati City

grace.grumo12@gmail.com

+63-955-140-5749

m www.linkedin.com/in/grace-grumo

www.github.com/grcgrm

www.behance.net/gracegrumo

ABOUT ME

I am a web developer with one year of professional experience who has a both creative side and logical skills. An individual who is skilled in developing visually appealing and functional websites. I am a very fast-learner and is always eager to learn new technologies when given the opportunity. A productive and efficient worker who values the time and opinions of the superiors.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Bachelor's degree STI College **2018-2022**

General Academic Strand

Senior High School STI College 2016-2018

Achievements

- Cum Laude
- Dean's Lister, 3 semesters
- President Lister, 3 semesters

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

KMC Savills Inc. - Bonifacio Global City, Philippines

August 2022-June 2023

Responsible for managing multiple large sites using Umbraco CMS, creating landing pages, and building new sites for clients using different technologies. Provide technical recommendations to improve the existing architecture, maintain the server for websites, and ensure timely delivery of development projects. Also work on improving site performance, assist in SEO practices, and provide web analytics reports to the team.

Web Developer

March 2022-July 2022

Breddas Inc. - Bonifacio Global City, Philippines

Works closely with the Lead Web Developer to create a new platform for the company and translates these requirements to the operational team. I participate in program design. Responsible for both front-end and back-end development of the platform, ensuring it is user-friendly and runs smoothly. I utilize a variety of markup languages to write web pages and ensure that user input is validated before submitting it to the back end.

PROJECTS

KMC Savills Website (kmcmaggroup.com) Umbraco CMS Version 7.12.3 The official corporate website of KMC Savills Role: Front-end Web Developer, Application Support, Server Management Technology Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Visual Studio, C#, ASP.Net MVC, Github, Microsoft SQL Server, IIS, Windows Server, Hubspot, Bootstrap, Google Map API, Google Analytics, Google Search Console	Aug 2022-Present
T1 Project Management (t1projectmanagement.com) Wordpress Official Website of T1 Project Management Role: Front-End Developer Technology Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Wordpress, PHP	Sep 2022-Present
Batangas Properties (kmcmaggroup.com/for-lease/batangas/) Umbraco CMS Version 7.12.3 Landing page for all property listings in Batangas Role: Front-end Web Developer Technology Stack: Umbraco, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Hubspot, Bootstrap, Google Analytics	May 2023-May 2023
PBCom Tower (kmcmaggroup.com/for-lease/pbcom-tower/) Umbraco CMS Version 7.12.3 Exclusive Landing Page for PBCom Tower in Makati Role: Front-end Web Developer Technology Stack: Umbraco, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Hubspot, Bootstrap, Google Analytics, Google Map API	April 2023-April 2023
Lead Microservice - Private ASP.NET Web Application API, C# API for leads connecting to KMC website and portal Role: Full Stack Developer Technology Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Visual Studio, C#, ASP.Net MVC, ASP.Net API, Swagger, Azure, Github, IIS, Windows Server, Hubspot, Bootstrap	Mar 2023-Mar 2023
KMC Savills Queuing System - Private ASP.NET Web Application, C# Ticketing system for all the support team of KMC Savills Role: Full Stack Developer Technology Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Visual Studio, C#, ASP.Net MVC, Github, Microsoft SQL Server, IIS, Windows Server, Azure	Jan 2023-Feb 2023
One Trium Tower (onetrium.kmcmaggroup.com) Umbraco CMS Version 7.12.3 Landing Page for One Trium Tower Role: Front-end Web Developer, Server Management Technology Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Visual Studio, C#, ASP.Net MVC, Github, IIS, Windows Server, Hubspot, Bootstrap, Google Map API	Aug 2022-Sep 2022

SKILLS

Programming Languages

- ✓ HTML
- ✓ CSS
- ✓ Bootstrap
- ✓ PHP
- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ C#
- ✓ MySQL

Framework

- ✓ Laravel
- ✓ Codelgniter
- ✓ ASP.NET
- ✓ Yii2

Hosting Tools

- ✓ Hostinger
- ✓ Heroku

Creative Tools

- ✓ Adobe XD
- ✓ Adobe Photoshop
- ✓ Adobe Illustrator
- ✓ Figma
- ✓ Adobe XD

CMS

- ✓ Umbraco
- ✓ Wordpress
- ✓ Shopify

Google Apps

- ✓ Google Maps API
- ✓ Google Search Console
- ✓ Google Analytics

Others

- ✓ MS Office
- ✓ Microsoft Clarity
- ✓ Hubspot
- ✓ Remote Server

Version Control Tools

- ✓ Git
- ✓ Github

Reference

Lance Concepcion

Senior Technical Engineer (KMC Savills)

Mobile: 09451847066

Email: lancelot.concepcion@gmail.com